Guide to the Noël Riley Fitch Julia Child Papers MSS.323
Fales Library and Special Collections
Noël Riley Fitch Julia Child Papers
1912-2018
Fales Library and Special Collections
Fitch, Noel Riley
MSS.323
26.84 Linear Feet in 29 boxes and 1 oversize folder in shared housing
Noël Riley Fitch (1937- ) is an author and biographer. She was Professor of Literature (1971-1987) and Chair of the Department of Literature and Modern Languages (1982-1985) at Point Loma College, and has lectured at the University of Southern California (1986-2007) and the American University of Paris (1987-2007). The Noël Riley Fitch Julia Child Papers consists largely of material related to the research, production, and reception of Appetite for Life: The Biography of Julia Child. These materials include correspondence, research, original letters and diaries of Julia and Paul Child, photographs, proofs and drafts of the manuscript. The collection also includes material related to the research and publication of her books The Grand Literary Cafés of Europe, Literary Cafés of Paris, and Paris Cafe: the Select Crowd. Personal materials related to the professional life of Fitch are in this collection, as well as a selection of menus from restaurants across Europe and the United States.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Noel Riley Fitch in 2011, 2013, and 2018. The accession numbers related to this gift are 2011.323, 2013.323, 2019.008.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into nine series, some of which have been further divided into subseries:
Series I. Appetite for Life: The Biography of Julia Child
Subseries A. Research Files
Subseries B. Research Correspondence
Subseries C. Drafts and Proofs
Subseries D. Publication, Publicity, and Reception
Subseries E. Photographs and Images
Series II. The Grand Literary Cafés of Europe
Series III. Literary Cafés of Paris
Series IV. Paris Café: The Select Crowd
Series V. Noël Riley Fitch Personal Materials
Series VI: Audio
Series VII: Video
Series VIII. Data Storage
Series IX. Objects
Biographical Note
Noël Riley Fitch (1937-) was born in New Haven, Connecticut, and educated at Northwest Nazarene College (B.A., 1959) and Washington State University (M.A., 1965 and Ph.D., 1969), and subsequently completed postdoctoral NEH seminar studies at Princeton (1976) and Yale (1979). She was professor of literature (1971-1987) and chair of the Department of Literature and Modern Languages (1982-1985) at Point Loma College. She was a lecturer at the University of Southern California from 1986 to 2007 and the American University of Paris from 1987 to 2007.
Working with the full cooperation and exclusive authorization of Julia Child, Noël Riley Fitch conducted thorough research into Child's life and completed extensive interviews with those in her broad circle to write Appetite for Life: The Biography of Julia Child (1997, 2012). Fitch went on to write further articles about Child and collaborated with the A&E Biography of her produced in 1997.
Fitch is also the author of a number of books exploring cafe culture in Europe and particularly Paris including The Grand Literary Cafes of Europe (2007), covering the history of coffee and the coffeehouse and featuring nearly 40 cafes in 20 countries, from London To Moscow, Lisbon to Bucharest and Rome; Literary Cafes of Paris (1989) with descriptions, history, anecdotes, and comments on the food and drink of nearly thirty establishments central to the literary life of France, America and England; and Paris Cafe: The Select Crowd (2007), a personal look into the workings and daily rhythm of a cafe and its famous as well as anonymous clientele co-authored with illustrator Rick Tulka.
Other major works by Fitch include Anaïs: The Erotic Life of Anaïs Nin (1993), Hemingway in Paris: Parisian Walks for the Literary Traveller (1989) and Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation: A History of Literary Paris in the Twenties and Thirties (1983). In addition, she co-edited, with Richard Etulain, Faith and Imagination (1985, 2012) and she published numerous articles, including [four] about Julia Child:
"Meanwhile: America honors its favorite 'French Chef'," International Herald Tribune. 24 July 2003.
"Notre Dame de la cuisine and the Prince des Gastronomes," Gastronomica; The Journal of Food and Culture. Summer, 2005: 73-79. "Child at Heart," Paris Notes. Cover essay. March, 2007.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Audiovisual and born-digital materials have not been preserved and are not available to researchers.
Related Archival Collections
Julia Child Papers. MC 644. Schlesinger Library, Radcliffe Institute, Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
Noël Riley Fitch Papers. Harry Ransom Center, University of Texas at Austin.
Noël Riley Fitch Papers, Department of Rare Books and Special Collections, Princeton University Library.
Scope and Content
The Noël Riley Fitch Julia Child Papers consist largely of material related to the research, production and reception of Appetite for Life: The Biography of Julia Child, including transcripts and audio tapes of interviews with Julia Child and her colleagues, family and friends; extensive correspondence related to research for the book; photocopies of original letters and diaries of Julia and Paul Child; newspaper and magazine articles and photocopies of books related to French cooking, cookery in the United States, various places that Julia Child lived, and organizations with which she was associated including the United States Office of Strategic Services and the American Institute of Wine and Food; photographs of Julia Child, her family and friends, as well as photographs taken in the course of research; proofs and drafts of the manuscript; and correspondence and documents related to the publication and publicity of Appetite for Life, including reviews and related correspondence post publication of the book. The collection also includes correspondence, clippings, source material, drafts and documents related to the research and publication of The Grand Literary Cafés of Europe, Literary Cafés of Paris and Paris Cafe: the Select Crowd, and personal materials related to the professional life of Noël Riley Fitch, as well as a collection of menus from restaurants across Europe and the United States.
Food habits; Food writers.; Food industry and trade; Floppy disks.; Editor author correspondence.; Printed ephemera.; Dinners and dining; Drafts (documents); Correspondence.; Culinary industry.; Cooking, American |x California style; Cooking, American; Authors and publishers |z United States |x History |y 20th century.; Biographies.; Audiocassettes.; Audiotapes.; Coffeehouses in literature.; Coffeehouses |z Europe.; Menus.; Interviews.; Women cooks -- United States.; Videocassettes.; Scrapbooks.; Reviews (document genre); Restaurants |z France |z Paris; Personal correspondence.; Newsletters.; Manuscripts for publication.; Food writing.; Cooking, French; Women cooks |z United States |x History |y 20th century.; Cooking, American -- History -- 20th century.; Cooking |x Study and teaching; Compact discs.; Cookbooks.; Comic books, strips, etc.; Caricatures.; Cambridge (Mass.); Books.; Book jackets.; Biography as a literary form.; Cooking schools.; Paris (France) |x History |y 20th century; Paris (France); Passports.; Periodicals.; Photocopies.; Photographs.; Administrative records.; Articles.; Print proof; Women in the food industry.; Fitch, Noel Riley; Child, Julia
- Series I: Appetite for Life: The Biography of Julia Child, 219572
  Scope and Content
  This series consists of correspondence, newspaper and magazine clippings, interview transcripts, photographs, photocopies of original letters and diaries, legal documents, manuscript drafts, proofs, notes and publicity materials. It also contains post-publication materials including correspondence and reviews responding to the book, correspondence relating to film rights, and materials related to articles and writing by Noël Riley Fitch about Julia Child after completion of the biography.
  - Subseries A: Research Files, 219573
    Subseries A: Research Files is arranged primarily following the structure of Appetite for Life, which loosely corresponds to the chronology of Julia Child's life. Research materials about Julia Child subsequent to the publication of Appetite for Life are arranged chonologically. The subseries consists of magazines and newspaper clippings related to Julia Child's life, work, and influences; photocopies of original diaries and letters of Paul and Julia Child; and notes and segments of transcripts from interviews conducted by Noël Riley Fitch about Julia Child.
    - Table of Contents Titles, undated; 226815 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Introduction - Julia Child, various; 226816 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Openings, [c1994]; 226818 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Birth - Childhood, 1912+; 226811 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Childhood / Food, various; 226822 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Physical Description, undated; 226823 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Pasadena History, [c1994]; 226824 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Mrs. Davis' Montessori School, Fall 1915 - June 1921; 226825 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1207 South Pasadena House (Now #1199), 1918, 1994; 226827 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Montecito Park - Summers Camp Asoleado, 1927 - 1931; 226828 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Poly Tech, 1993 - 1994; 226834 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Stevens Murder, 1927, 1926 - 1927, November 1993; 226835 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - KBS - History [Katharine Branson School, 1917 - 1945], 1976, 1989; 226836 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Katharine Branson School, 1927 - 1930, 1994; 226837 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Smith College, 1930 - 1934, 1994, 1996; 226838 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1934 June - 1935 June, 1996; 226839 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Julia C. McWilliams Locked Diary [Photocopies], 1936; 226840 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - La France a Table: Table Tourisme Santé (Julia Child's Subscription), June 1935; 226842 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Sloans W&J NYC - September 1935 - August 1937, 1935 - 1937, 1994; 226851 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Writings 1938 - 1942: Coast Junior League, 1938 - 1942, 1996; 226854 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Portion of Julia McWilliams' Diary [Photocopies], 1936, 1941; 226856 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Pasadena Pre-War: 1937 May - 1942 July, Mother's Death, 1993; 226863 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Washington - Donovan: 1942 August (Pre-Ceylon), 1942 - 1943, 1990 - 1995; 226864 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Foreign Service: 1943 - 1945, 1989, 1994, 2008; 226865 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Paul Child: Journal - Starts March 11, 1943 [Photocopies, 1 of 2], 226866 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Paul Child: Journal - Starts March 11, 1943 [Photocopies, 2 of 2], 226867 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Julia McWilliams: "Oh So Private" Diary [Photocopies], 1944; 226868 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Paul Child: India - Letters to Charlie Child March 6, 1944 - January 18, 1945 [Photocopies, 1 of 2], 1944 - 1945; 226869 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Paul Child: India - Letters to Charlie Child March 6, 1944 - January 18, 1945 [Photocopies, 1 of 2], 1944 - 1945; 226870 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Original Letters of Paul Child to Charlie Child: New Delhi, Kandy, China, 1944 - 1945; 226871 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Ceylon 1944 April - 1945 March [Letters Not Included], 1992 - 1996; 226872 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - China 1945 March - October, 1945, 1953, 1999; 226875 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - China 1945 (& Home - S.F.) 10 January - 25 November (Pearl Harbor) [Photocopies, 1 of 2], 226879 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - China 1945 (& Home - S.F.) 10 January - 25 November (Pearl Harbor) [Photocopies, 2 of 2], 226880 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Paul Child: Foreign Service Documents [Photocopies], 1944 - 1945; 226884 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - China to East Coast [Application for Federal Employment], undated; 226885 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Phila Miller O'Melvany "Mother" 8 May 1946+, 1954, undated; 226893 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Paul Child 1943+, 1942 - 1943, 1968; 226897 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Paul at Avon 1931 - 1942, 1931 - 1942, 1994 - 1996; 226899 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Paul's Paintings, 1996; 226900 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Edith Kennedy (Joan Brewster Letter, Photocopies), 1942, 1994; 226901 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Childs - Paul / Charlie, 1986, 1993 - 1994; 226902 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Julia McWilliams Employment Data [Photocopies], 1944; 226903 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Pasadena 1945 December - 1946 June [Original Letters by Paul Child to Julia Child, 1 of 2], 1945 - 1946, 1996; 226905 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Pasadena 1945 December - 1946 June [Original Letters by Paul Child to Julia Child, 2 of 2], 1945 - 1946; 226906 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Leaving Home CA - East / Maine 1946 July [Photocopies], 226907 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Maine, 1994 - 1996; 226908 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Marriage September 12 Noon 1946, 1946, 1996; 226911 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Washington DC - Georgetown 1946 - 1948, 1946 - 1948, 1994; 226914 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Lumberville Coopernose, 1959, 1997; 226916 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - The Joy of Cooking: Rombauer [Clipping], June 1994; 226917 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Arrival - Paris 1948, 1948, 1993; 226918 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - French Cooking 1948+, 226920 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Child - Restaurants France, 1994, 1996; 226923 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Paris Miscellaneous 1948 - 1953 [Julia Child's Original Diaries 1948, 1950], 1947 - 1953, 1994; 226929 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Paris Markets & Home Cooking, 1995; 226930 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Le Cordon Bleu 1949 Ocotber - 1950 March, 1949 - 1950, 1995; 226931 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1949 [Letters, Original Address Book and Planner], 1948 - 1949; 226932 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Le Cordon Bleu [Demonstration Programs], 1950, 1994 - 1995; 226933 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - 1950 France [Original Julia Child Letters from Mediterranean to Paul Child], undated, 1950; 226934 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - 1951 Paris [Address Book, Diary, Original Letters from Paul Child to Julia Child], 226936 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - 1950 Letters by Paul Child to Julia Child [Photocopies], 226938 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Ivan Cousins Paris, undated; 226942 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - England - Christmas Food, 1950, 1994; 226943 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Beck, Simone 1951+, various; 226945 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - L'école es Trois Gourmandes (The School of the Three Happy Eaters), 1952 - 1954, 1982, 1995; 226957 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Escoffier - Carême, 1955, 1996; 226958 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Paris 1952 [Original Planner, Letters Photocopies], 1952 - 1953, undated; 226959 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Early Cook Book 1952, 1952, 1991; 226960 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Schlesinger Letters from Julia Child and Paul Child, "Paulski Diaries" [Photocopies, 1 of 4], 1952 - 1953; 226961 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Schlesinger Letters from Julia Child and Paul Child, "Paulski Diaries" [Photocopies, 2 of 4], 1952 - 1953; 226962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Schlesinger Letters from Julia Child and Paul Child, "Paulski Diaries" [Photocopies, 3 of 4], 1952 - 1953; 226963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Schlesinger Letters from Julia Child and Paul Child, "Paulski Diaries" [Photocopies, 4 of 4], 1952 - 1953; 226964 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Schlesinger - "Paulski Diaries" 1953 Pre-Marseille, 226965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Marseille 1953 February - 1954 September [Original Address Book and Planner, 1 of 2], 1953 - 1954, 1995; 226966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Marseille 1953 February - 1954 September [Original Letter, 2 of 2], 1953 - 1954, 1995; 226967 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Bonn 1954 October - 1956 October [Original Planner], 1954 - 1956, 1997; 226968 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Bonn 1955, 1955, 1994 - 1995; 226969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Investigation of Paul 1995 April [Original Planner, Letters], 1955, 1995; 226970 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - "Paulski Diaries" 1954 [Photocopies], 226971 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - FBI Documents on Paul Child [Photocopies], 1954 - 1955, 2002; 226972 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Bonn 1956 [Original Planner], 1956, 1995; 226973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - De Voto's 1952 - 1953, 1952 - 1953, 1982, 1992; 226974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Washington DC November 1956 - 1957, 1956 - 1957, 1996; 226975 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Washington DC 1958 [Original Planner], 226976 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Washington DC - Norway 1959, 226977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Oslo, Norway 1959+ [Photocopies, 1 of 2], 226978 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Oslo, Norway 1959+ [Photocopies, 2 of 2], 226979 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Oslo, Norway 1960 - Cooking Classes, 1960, 1995; 226980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - House 103 Irving, 1966, 1997; 226981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Boston 1956 [Original Address Book], 1956, 1980, 1993 - 1994; 226982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Oslo, Norway 1961 July, 1961, 1995; 226989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - 1961 August - Book Launching [Original Planner], 226995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Kitchen, 1962; 226998 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Mastering the Art I, 1953, 1961, undated; 227000 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Knopf, 1996; 227006 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Julia Child Letters to Simca [Photocopies, 1 of 2], 1960 - 1964; 227011 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Julia Child Letters to Simca [Photocopies, 2 of 2], 1960 - 1964; 227012 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Paul Child Letters to Chas [Photocopies, 1 of 2], 1960; 227013 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Paul Child Letters to Chas [Includes Letters from Julia Child, Photocopies, 2 of 2], 1960; 227014 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Knopf Letters [Photocopies, Publishing Tour Proofs], 1961; 227015 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Claiborne, Craig, 1992 - 1996; 227016 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Breadloaf Writers' Conference 1961+, 1960s, 1990s; 227018 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - 1960s, 1995 - 1997; 227022 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - 1962 [Original Planner], 1962, 1994 - 1995; 227025 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - 1963 [Original Letters], 1963, 1995; 227026 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Public Television, 1962, 1993 - 1997; 227027 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - "The French Chef" WGBH 1962 Pilot - 1963 Series, 1962 - 1964, 1995 - 1996; 227028 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Elizabeth David (b. 1913), 1963 - 1964, 1992 - 1995; 227032 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - La Pitchoune 1962+, various; 227036 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - 1964 [Original Planner, Letters], 227037 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Letters 1964 January - December [Photocopies], 227038 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Letters 1965 January - December [Photocopies], 227043 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - 1965 Time Cover, Peabody [Original Planner, Letters], 227048 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - 1966 [Original Planner, 1 of 2], 227052 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - 1966 [2 of 2], 227055 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Paul's Food Role (Child in 1966), 1994 - 1995; 227064 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Field, Michael Time-Life (SIMCA) [Original Letters], 1966; 227065 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Volume II - Mastering the Art (1970), Preparation Letters (1966) [Original Documentation] (1 of 2), various; 227067 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Volume II - Mastering the Art (1970), Preparation Letters (1966) [Original Documentation] (2 of 2), various; 270480 (Box 5, Folder 3a)
    - Beard, James: Beard House 1964, various; 227068 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - M.F.K. Fisher, 1990s; 227069 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - The French Chef Cookbook 1968, 1968, undated; 227070 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Simca's Recipes, Julia's Recipes [Original Documentation], 1966 - 1970; 227071 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 1967 January - June [Photocopies, 1 of 2], 227072 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - 1967 January - June [Originals and Photocopies, 1 of 2], 227073 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - White House, 1967, undated; 227074 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - 1967 July - December [Original Planner, Letters], 227075 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Original Address Book, "J. Office Cambridge 1968", 227076 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - 1968 - The French Chef Book [Original Planner, Photocopies, 1 of 2], 227077 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - 1968 - The French Chef Book [Photocopies, 2 of 2], 227078 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - 1969 January - May [Original Letters], 227079 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - 1969 June - December [Original Planner, Letters, Recipes], 227080 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - 1970 January - May [Photocopies], 1970, 1995; 227081 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - 1970s, various; 227082 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - French Chef in France: 1970 May, 227083 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - 1968 - Mastering the Art II 1970, 1968, undated; 227084 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Charles Child to Paul & Sandra Sheeline Chiefly [Photocopies], 1970s; 227085 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - 1970 June - December [Original Letter], 227086 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - 1971 January - May [Original Letters], 227087 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - 1971 June - December [Photocopies], 227088 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - 1972 [Photocopies], 1972, 1996; 227089 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - French Chef Miscellaneous BBC '73, 1973; 227090 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 1973 January - May [Original Letters, Photocopies], 227091 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 1973 June - December [Photocopies], 227092 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Paul's Illness 1974+, various; 227093 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 1974 [Originals, Photocopies], 1974, 1996; 227094 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Bubbles From the Spring by Paul Child [Photocopy], 1974; 227095 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Nouvelle Cuisine, 1977, undated; 227096 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 1975 Clippings [Originals, Photocopies], 227097 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 1975 - From Julia Child's Kitchen [Clippings, Notes], 227098 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - 1976 [Original Letters], 1976, 1996; 227176 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Women in Food - Feminism, undated, 1975, 1996; 227178 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - La Varenne - Opened 11/1974, Julia Child Visits 12/1975 [Photocopies], undated, 1974; 227189 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - 1977 [Original Itinerary], 1977 - 1978, 1996; 227192 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - McCalls 1977 - 1982, 1970, 1994; 227193 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Hesse 1977, 1975, 1977; 227194 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - 1978, 1974,1978, 1994; 227195 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Saturday Night Live: December 1978, 1996; 227196 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Julia Child + Company TV Book 1978, 1979. 1995 - 1996; 227197 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Julia Child + More Company 1978, 1980, 1994; 227198 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - 1979, 227199 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - 1980s, 1994, 1997; 227200 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Clippings - 1980 [Original Letters], 227201 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Good Morning America: 1980 - 1981, 1981, 1996; 227205 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Blanquette de Veau, various; 227206 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - White House: 1984, various; 227218 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - JC Place in Food World, 1990; 227219 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Santa Barbara Looking West: 1981, 1994, 1996; 227220 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - 1981, 1981, 1996; 227222 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - A.I.W.F. Founding: 1981 - 1983, 1981 - 1983, 1996; 227228 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Mondavi - Great Chefs: 1981 - 1986, 1982, 1996; 227231 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Parade: February 1982, 227234 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - 1982 [Original Itinerary], 1982, 1996; 227237 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - 1983 [Original Letters], 227255 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Dinner at Julia's: Tapes 1983, 227256 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - 1984, 1984, 1996; 227257 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - A.I.W.F. - The Great Gatsby: 1984 - 1988, 1986, 1996; 227258 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Clippings - 1985 Honorary Degree, 1985, 1994 - 1996; 227259 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Journal of Gastronomy: July 1984, 1984, 1996; 227262 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - 1986, 1986, 1996; 227264 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - 1987, 1987 - 1988, 1996; 227266 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - 1988, 1968, 1988, 1995; 227267 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - "Bon Appétit!" Play, 1989, 1991; 227269 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Boston University - 1987+, 1991, 1995 - 1996; 227270 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - A.I.W.F. - Revolution (1987) 1988 - 1989, 1989, 1995; 227271 (Box 6, Folder 44)